INGREDIENTS Nutrition

SERVINGS: 4 and UNITS: US
2 lbs boneless chicken breasts, cut into bite-size pieces
1 -2 tablespoon olive oil
1 garlic clove, crushed
1⁄4 teaspoon ginger
3⁄4 teaspoon crushed red pepper flakes
1⁄4 cup apple juice
1⁄3 cup light brown sugar
2 tablespoons ketchup
1 tablespoon cider vinegar
1⁄2 cup water
1⁄3 cup soy sauce

or 
SERVINGS: 4 and UNITS: Metric
907.18 g boneless chicken breasts, cut into bite-size pieces
14.79-29.58 ml olive oil
1garlic clove, crushed
1.23 ml ginger
3.69 ml crushed red pepper flakes
59.14 ml apple juice
78.07 ml light brown sugar
29.58 ml ketchup
14.79 ml cider vinegar
118.29 ml water
78.07 ml soy sauce

DIRECTIONS

Editor's Note: Named Bourbon Chicken because it was supposedly created by a Chinese cook who worked in a restaurant on Bourbon Street.
Heat oil in a large skillet.
Add chicken pieces and cook until lightly browned.
Remove chicken.
Add remaining ingredients, heating over medium Heat until well mixed and dissolved.
Add chicken and bring to a hard boil.
Reduce heat and simmer for 20 minutes.
Serve over hot rice and ENJOY.